

Nina Zanarelli

Professional Summary

Creative Designer with 2 years of experience working in the UI and Service Design field. Achievments include winning the McGinnis Competition award of March 2021 and the Social Venture Plan Competition award on April 2021. Original and clever with the ability to lead large design and development teams.

Work History

Fifth Beat - UX/UI Designer Intern

Rome, Italy

02/2022 - Current

- Evaluated user research to convert abstract ideas and requirements into planning tools such as journey maps, user personas and mobile and desktop interfaces.
- Collaborated with teammates to deliver valuable features meeting business and customer needs.

Intra Startup - Chief Designer

Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania 03/2020 - 10/2021

- Developed design deliverables that elevated, differentiated and functioned on-brand and on-strategy.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere.

LookUp - LookUp Social Innovator

United States

12/2020 - 06/2021

- Won a highly selective US competition.
- Worked with highly-respected executive mentor to transform ideas into actions to affect social change and a more humane digital world.

Politecnico di Milano - Salone del Mobile Volunteer

Milan, Italy

04/2019 - 05/2019

• Utilized great communication and interpersonal skills when interacting with parties to promote Politecnico's design artefacts.

V&A Dundee - International Workshop

Dundee, Scotland 02/2019 - 02/2019

 Quickly learned new service design skills and applied them to daily tasks while working with an international team. nina.zanarelli@gmail.com

+393483615850

Milan, Italy 20147

Portfolio

https://nina.zanarelli.github.io/

Skills

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Creative design layouts
- Customized template design
- Illustration
- Teamwork skills
- Project presentations

Education

Expected in 10/2022

Politecnico di Milano

Milan, Italy

Master of Arts: Product Service System Design

07/2020

Politecnico di Milano

Milan, Italy

Bachelor of Arts: Interior Design

07/2017

Scientific High School - Vittorio Veneto

Milan, Italy

High School Diploma